Henry-Russell Hitchcock
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Chronological Name and Subject Files, 1919-1987, Series 2:; (Boxes 1-22; 21.9 linear ft.)
  Holser, Clifford B. (1952)
  Holt, Rinehart and Winston (1972)
  Holzbog, Tom (1967)
  Homolka, Larry J. (1965-1967)
  Hooker, Arthur (1952)
  Honour, Hugh (1966)
  Hood, Graham (1971)
  Hooker, John (1953)
  Hooper, S. C. (1954)
  Hoover, Donald (1952)
  Hoover, Kathleen O'Donnell (1948-1949, 1951)
  Hope, Henry R. (1943, 1945-1950, 1954, 1957, 1959, 1962)
  Hopping, D.M.C. (1955-1956)
  Hordczak, Theodore (1956)
  Horn, Estelle (1950)
  Horn, Milton (1946, 1949, 1951-1952)
  Horn, Walter (1958)
  Horne, Mr. and Mrs. Bernard S. (1955)
  Hornsey, Borough of (1946)
  Horsburgh, Patrick (1952-1955)
  Horta Committee (1960)
  Hosken, Franziska Porges (1963)
  Hotel Grande Bretagne (1961)
  Hotel Inghilterra (1961)
  Housend, Brian (1956)
  House Beautiful (1928)
  Housing (1945)
  Houston (1959, 1967)
  Houston, University of (1953-1954)
  Howard, Charles (1956)
  Howard, Tom (1945)
  Howard University (1961-1962)
  Howarth, Thomas (1953-1957, 1959-1960, 1962-1963, 1966)
  Howe, George (1945, 1949, 1951, 1953)
  Howe, Hester (1954, 1956)
  Howe, Lawrence (1955)
  Howe, Mrs. Lawrence (1945)
  Howe, Stewart S. (1954)
  Howe, Thomas C. (1953, 1954)
  Howlett, D. Roger (1965)
  Howland, Richard H. (1952-1954, 1959, 1961)
  Hoyle, Henry D. (1969)
  Hoyt, Deming (1960)
  Hoyt, Natalie (1947, 1949-1951, 1956, 1959, 1963)
  Hoyt, Nelly (1968)
  Hubbard, L. Kent (1937)
  Hubbard, R. J. (1959)
  Hubbard, Ray (1978)
  Hubbard, Russell (1949)
  Huber, Erna (1963-1964, 1966, 1970-1971)
  Huber, Erna and Charlie (1983)
  Hudnut, Claire (1948)
  Hudnut, Helen (1947-1948)
  Hudnut, Joseph (1945, 1951)
  Hudson River Conservancy Society, Inc. (1945)
  Huemer, Frances (1955)
  Huff, William S. (1958, 1965)
  Hughenden Manor (1950)
  Hughes, Richard (1953-1954)
  Hughes, Talmadge C. (1945)
  [Hugnet?], Georges (undated)
  Hulst, Roger d' (1973)
  Hulton Press (1957)
  Hundertmark, Dieter (1960)
  Hunn, Robert (1970)
  Hunter, Anna C. (1955)
  Hunter, Bob (1954)
  Huntington, C. (1955)
  Huntington, Constant (1952)
  Huntington, David C. (1961, 1963-1965, 1967-1968, 1971)
  Huntington, J. D. (1951)
  Huntington, James L. (1954-1955, 1957-1959, 1963-1965)
  Huntington, John (1955)
  Huntington, Trudy (1952)
  Huse, Norbert (1975)
  Hussey, Alfred R. (1949)
  Hussey, Mary (1954, 1962)
  Huxley Brothers (1951, 1954)
  Huxtable, Ada Louise (1947, 1950, 1957-1958, 1961-1962, 1969, 1971, 1982-1983)
  Hyams, N. (1948)
  Hyde Hall, Inc., Friends of (1965)
  Hyman, Isabelle (1977)
  Iber, Howard John (1972, 1974)
  Illinois Institute of Technology (1950, 1954)
  Illinois, University of (1947, 1949, 1965, 1979)
  Ilmanen, William (1954, 1956)
  Imperial Institute (1956)
  Inaya, Beata (1956)
  In the Nature of Materials (1968-1969) (see also: Wright, Frank Lloyd)
  Income Tax (1956-1957, 1972)
  India International Center (1964-1965)
  Indiana University (1948, 1953, 1966)
  Indiana, University of (1945, 1961)
  Indianapolis, Art Association of (1948)
  Information Agency, U.S. (1955)
  Information Service, U.S. (1961)
  Inghilterra Hotel (1960)
  Inglis, F. C. (1954)
  Ingraham, David (1941)
  Ingraham, Henry A. (1945, 1947)
  Innendekoration (1963)
  Inspector of Foreign Dividends (1956)
  Inscoe, Eva Jane (1983)
  Institute for Advanced Studies (1963)
  Institute for Architecture and Urban Studies (1975)
  Institute of Contemporary Art (1948-1949, 1953-1954, 1956, 1961, 1963-1964, 1976)
  Institute of Fine Arts, New York University (1949, 1956-1957, 1960, 1967) (see also: New York University)
  Institute of International Education (1955)
  Institute of Landscape Architects (1952)
  Instituto di Storia dell'Arte (1961)
  Instituto Italiano di Cultura (1958)
  Instituto per la Collaborazione Culturale (1965) (see also: Collaborazione Culturale, Instituto per la)
  Insurance (1970)
  Insurance Company of America (1963)
  Intercultural Publications, Inc. (1953)
  International Architecture Students Conference (1949)
  International Congress of African Studies (see: African Studies, International Congress of)
  International Encyclopedia of Architecture, Engineering, and Urban Planning (1976-1977)
  International Design Conference (1955)
  International Information Administration (1952)
  International Publications, Inc. (1954)
  International Union of Architects, Sixth Congress (1960)
  International University of Art (1970)
  Ireland, Royal Institute of Architects of (1962)
  Irving, Robert Grant (1968)
  Irvy, Benjamin (1981)
  Isham, Gyles (1954)
  Isis (1961, 1964)
  Isley, Natelle (1956)
  Italian Institute (1956)
  Ivins, William M. (1936)
  Jack, William A. Park (1936)
  Jackson, Esther (1953)
  Jacobi, Frank (1952)
  Jacobs Antiques (1948-1949)
  Jacobs, Robert A. (1965)
  Jacobs, Stephen (1966)
  Jacobus, John [Jake] (1957-1962, 1964-1966, 1969-1971, 1980-1981)
  Jacobus, John [Jake] and Marion (1963)
  Jaffe, Michael (1952-1956, 1958-1964, 1966, 1968, 1973, 1977, 1986)
  Jaffe, Ronald (1952)
  James, Evan (1946)
  James, George (1952)
  James, Philip (1952, 1958)
  Jamieson, K. I. (1953)
  Janis Gallery (1949)
  Janis, Sidney (1950)
  Jansen, Dick (1953-1954, 1961-1962)
  Jansen, Dick and Ellen (1955)
  Janson, H. W. (1959-1962, 1972, 1975, 1977, 1983)
  Janson, Peter (1978, 1982)
  Jarrett, James (1958-1959, 1981)
  Jeannert, Marie-Louise (1982)
  Jefferson National Expansion Memorial (1947)
  Jemma, Manuela (1965)
  Jenkins, Frank I. (1955-1956, 1958, 1960-1961, 1964-1967)
  Jennings, Nancy Gillespie (1970)
  Jerome Hotel (1955)
  Jerome, T. T. (1947)
  Jersey City, N. J. (1981)
  Jewell, Jim (1953, 1956)
  Joedicke, Jurgen (1963)
  Johanneson, Eric (1969)
  John, Dorothy (1954)
  Johns Hopkins University (1952, 1965, 1967-1971, 1973-1975)
  Johnson Art Collection (1926-1927)
  Johnson, Buffie (1948)
  Johnson, Donald Leslie (1977)
  Johnson Gallery, Museum of Modern Art (1984)
  Johnson, J. R. (1969)
  Johnson, J. Stewart (1968, 1976)
  Johnson, James R. (1946-1951, 1953-1954, 1958-1959, 1966, 1978, 1983)
  Johnson, Laura (1945)
  Johnson, Margaret (1952)
  Johnson, Peter 1977, 1979
  Johnson, Philip C. (1934, 1945-1967, 1969, 1973, 1975, 1978-1979, 1981-1983, undated) (see also: Nineteenth Century American Architects [with Philip Johnson])
  Johnson Reprint Corp. (1973)
  Johnson, Robert H. (1947)
  Johnson, Thomas (1973)
  Johnson, W. (1958)
  Johnson, Wendell (1961-1966, 1973, 1980, 1982-1984)
  Johnson-Marshall, Percy and April (1960) (see also: Marshall, Percy Johnson)
  Johnsson, Ulf C. (1965)
  Johnston, Norman (1952)
  Jonals Co. (1958)
  Jones, Cranston (1958)
  Jones, Douglas (1966)
  Jones, Ernest (1957-1958)
  Jones, Mrs. Fred (1941)
  Jones, Howard M. (1958-1959)
  Jones, Martin R. (1956-1959, 1962)
  Jones, Ralph (1958)
  Jones Real Estate (1970)
  Jones, Robert 1959
  Jones, Ronald F. (1946)
  Jordy, William (1950-1962, 1964, 1968-1970, 1972-1973, 1976, 1978, 1981, 1983, undated)
  Joselit, David (1981)
  Journal of the History of Ideas (1955)
  Joyce, Henry (1980)
  Judkins, Winthrop (1971)
  Judson (1978)
  Judson, H. Richard (1965)
  Jules, Mervin (1962-1963, 1965, 1970)
  Kahn, Albert (1945-1946)
  Kahn, Charles (1978)
  Kahn, David M. (1975)
  Kahn, Louis I. (1960)
  Kahn, Moritz (1938)
  Kaiga Bunka Chuokyoku (1954)
  Kalamazoo Institute of Arts (1961)
  Kalec, Donald Gordon (1974-1976)
  Kallman, G. M. (1948)
  Kallman, Gerhard (1969)
  Kamys, Walter (1957, 1962)
  Kane, Amanda (1962)
  Kansas City Star (1964)
  Kansas State College (1955)
  Kapp, Helen (1956)
  Kantor, Sibyl (1980, 1982)
  Kardan, Sel (1985)
  Karl-Ernst-Osthaus-Museum (1956)
  Karlsruhe (1956, 1963)
  Karner, L. C. (1959)
  Karolik, Maxim (1952)
  Karpel, Bernard (1969)
  Karpinski, Caroline (1970)
  Karshner, Joseph H. (1957)
  Kates, George N. (1923, 1926-1928, 1930, 1945, 1948-1949, 1956, undated)
  Katz, Ruth B. (1953)
  Katzenellenbogen, Mrs. Adolph (1950)
  Kaufman, Emil (1953)
  Kaufmann, Edgar, Jr. (1942, 1944, 1947, 1952, 1960-1963, 1968, 1970, 1974-1978, 1981-1984, 1986)
  Kauter, Mat (1947)
  Keacer (1961)
  Kearns, G. W. (1953)
  Keating, Mary (1978)
  Keefe, John W. (1970)
  Keefe and Keefe 1985
  Keener, John P. (1947-1948)
  Keeney, Barbara (1955)
  Keiiti, Taira (1962)
  Keiser, George C. (1929, 1945, 1947, 1953, 1956)
  Keisern, George C. and Nancy (1948, 1951-1952, 1955)
  Keiser, Nancy (1957, 1962, 1970, 1972, 1974, 1976, 1979, 1983)
  Keith, Lucy (1953)
  Kelley, Charles H. (1979)
  Kelly, Burnham (1953-1954, 1964)
  Kennedy, Clarence (1972)
  Kennedy Fund (1963) (see also: Smith College)
  Kennedy, John F. (1953)
  Kennedy, Robert W. (1949-1950)
  Kennedy, Roger G. (1967)
  Kennedy, Ruth L. (1955-1956, 1958, 1961-1968, undated)
  Kentucky Engineer (1955)
  Kentucky, University of (1969)
  Kenyon Corn Meal Co. (1959)
  Kepes, George (1948)
  Kermacy, Martin S. (1956)
  Kerr, Chester (1951-1952)
  Kersting, A. F. (1971)
  Kestenbaum, Joy M. (1979, 1984-1985)
  Ketchum, Phillips (1949)
  Kettell, Russell (1954)
  Keyes, Margaret (1975)
  Kidney, Walter C. (1957, 1972-1973, 1983)
  Kihlstedt, Folke T. (1971, 1974, 1980)
  Killian, Tom (1983)
  Kimball, Fiske (1938, 1953-1955)
  Kinehardt, Sibley (1968)
  King and Chusman Insurance (1948)
  King, A. Rowden (1952)
  King, Anthony (1962-1963)
  King, May Abigail (1968)
  Kings College (1962)
  Kingston School of Art (1961)
  Kingzett, Richard (1961)
  Kirstein, Coco (1928)
  Kirstein, Lincoln (1928-1929, 1945, undated)
  Kissin, Meredith (1973)
  Kitchen (1960-1961)
  Kizar, John (1979)
  Klapper, Paul (1947)
  Kleinbauer, Eugene (1962)
  Klemm, Heinz (1964)
  Klinger, Timothy C. (1973)
  Knoedler and Co. (1951, 1955, 1968-1970)
  Knorre, Eckhard van (1971, 1973)
  Knowledge Publications (1966)
  Knowlton, John H. (1974)
  Knox, Brian (1981)
  Knox, Bruce (1972)
  Knoxville (1978)
  Koch, Carl (1947)
  Koch, Edward (1983)
  Koch, Robert (1958-1959)
  Kochen (undated)
  Koenig, Philip (1951)
  Kohn, Geraldine (1961)
  Koike, Shinji (1951-1952, 1955)
  Kolper, Fred (1956)
  Kommer, Bjorn (1964)
  Konsthistorisk Tidskrift (1937)
  Kootz, Samuel (1948)
  Kopcke, Guenter (1976)
  Korn, Thomas H. (1952)
  Kornegay, Bill (1961, 1963, 1969-1970, 1974, 1982-1983)
  Kornwolf, James D. (1977-1979)
  Kostof, Spero (1976)
  Kowsky, Francis (1978-1981)
  Kozlow, Robert D. (1951-1954, 1957)
  Kramer, Ellen (1950-1955, 1957-1958, 1960-1961, 1964, 1967-1969, 1971-1972, 1975)
  Kramer, Estel Thea (1976)
  Krautheimer, Richard (1945, 1947, 1950, 1952, 1957, 1961, 1963, 1965-1967, 1969, 1971, 1982)
  Krautheimer, Richard and Trude (1952)
  Kredler, Jack (1927)
  Kremer, Eugene (1965, 1967)
  Kremers, David Edward (1974)
  Krinsky, Carol Herselle (1981)
  Krom, Martha (1980)
  Kruft, Hanno-Walter 1984
  Kubler, George A. (1945-1946, 1949-1950, 1954-1957)
  Kuhn, Ethel (1964)
  Kultermann, Udo (1965)
  Kunhardt, Mr. and Mrs. (undated)
  Kunin, Jack Henry (1969)
  Kunstakedmiets Bibliotek (1956)
  Kunsthalle Bielfeld (1983) (see also: Bielfeld Kunsthalle)
  Kunstwerk (1957)
  Kwan, Michael (1972, 1975, 1977)
  Labo, Mario (1961)
  Lacoste, Gerald (1956)
  La Farge, Henry A. (1950, 1955)
  Lain, Alan K. (1946, 1977)
  Lamb, Deborah (1951)
  Lamb, Robert J. (1976)
  Lambert, Jean (1963-1966)
  Lambert, Phyllis (1974-1976, 1982, 1984)
  Lambert, R. J. (1960-1961)
  Lambert, Sam (1955)
  Lambs, S. R. (1952)
  Lamont, Corliss (1953)
  Lamont, Ruth (1960)
  Lancashire Society of Architects 1(962)
  Lancaster, Clay (1951-1953)
  Lancaster, Margaret (1949-1950)
  Land, Terre (1955)
  Landau, Sarah (1974-1986)
  Landesamt fur Denkmalpfleg Nord-Rhein-Westfalen (1956)
  Landmarks Conservancy, New York (1977, 1983)
  Landmarks Preservation Commission, City of New York (1970-1971, 1973, 1975, 1982, 1985)
  Landmarks Preservation Foundation, New York (1985)
  Landor, Walter (1940)
  Landy, Jacob (1957-1959, 1961-1963, 1966, 1970)
  Lane, Barbara Miller (1976-1977)
  Lane, Gilman (1941)
  Lane, Stephen (1948)
  Lang, S. (1956)
  Lang, Samuel (1970)
  Langenskiold, Eric (1960)
  Langrock Co. (1949-1950)
  Langsam, Walter E. (1966, 1968-1969)
  Langston, Jane (1978)
  Lanmon, Lorraine (1974)
  Larkin, Oliver (Pete) (1946-1947, 1949, 1951-1952, undated)
  Larkin, Oliver (Pete) and Ruth (1950)
  Larsen, Susan (1972)
  Lasdun, Denys (1940, 1954, 1958-1959, 1961-1962)
  Laskin (1981)
  Laskin, Myron (1974)
  Laskin, R. (1964-1965)
  Lasko, Peter (1982)
  Lasko, Viola (1955)
  Laubs, E. R. (1953)
  Lauder, Standish (1963, 1966)
  Laughlin, Clarence J. (1955)
  Laughlin, James (1953)
  Launder, Victor (1950)
  Laurent, Marge and Paul (1950)
  Law, Graham C. (1949-1951)
  Lawrence, Leslie (1943, 1945)
  Lazzaro, G. di San (1967)
  Lebold, Joan (1954-1955)
  Lebovich, Bill (1977)
  Leconte, Andre (1958)
  Le Corbusier (1936)
  Ledermann, P. (1958)
  Lee, Antoinette Josephine [Toni] (1975, 1982)
  Lee House (1948)
  Lee, Renselaer (1947)
  Lee, Sherman (1959)
  Leeb, Mr. and Mrs. Brian P. (1954)
  Leeds (1946)
  Leeds Architecture Students Association (1955)
  Leeper, John Palmer (1957)
  Leeuwen, Tom von (1974-1975, 1977)
  Lefevre Gallery (1982)
  Legge, Christopher (1953)
  Lehman, Arnold (1970)
  Lehmann, Karl (1952-1953)
  Lehmann, Karl and Phyllis (1955-1956)
  Lehmann, Phyllis W. (1949, 1951-1952, 1956, 1959-1960, 1965, 1968-1969, 1973, 1978, 1981)
  Lehmbruck, Manfred (1964)
  Leib, Norbert (1967)
  Leibner, Gernard (1973)
  Leibowitz, Herbert (1976)
  Leicester, University of (1963, 1966-1968, 1970)
  Leided, Rykstuniversiteit te (1966)
  Leigh, Roger ( 1955)
  Lemon, Sally (1954-1955, 1957)
  Lenn, Lottie H. (1951)
  Leonard, A. O. (1951)
  Leonard, J. C. (1957)
  Lerski, Hanna (1978)
  Lescaze, William E. (1928, 1937, undated)
  Levassor (1956)
  Lever House (1983)
  Lever, Jill 1986
  Levine, Neil (1972, 1976-1977, 1983)
  Levine, Seymour J. (1951)
  Levion, Sally (1954)
  Levy, Julien, Gallery (1946)
  Levy, S. Dean (1973, 1982)
  Lewine, Milton (1967)
  Lewis, David (1946)
  Lewis, Mrs. David (1945)
  Lewis, Lesley (1946, 1952)
  Lewis, Stanley T. (1952)
  Lewis, Virginia 1958
  Lewis, Wilmarth Sheldon (1948-1952, 1954, 1963)
  Li, Sue Yung (1956)
  Library (1968-1969)
  Library Company of Philadelphia (see: Philadelphia,
  Library Company of)
  Library of Congress (1940-1942, 1944, 1947)
  Lichebeelden Institute (1956-1958)
  Licht, Fred (1963)
  Liddell, Janet (1953)
  Lieb, Norbert (1971-1973)
  Liebert, Herman (1947, 1951)
  Lieberthal, Mary (1976)
  Lienhardt, Robert C. (1963)
  Life Magazine (1945-1946)
  Lilliput Magazine (1947)
  Limerick, Jeff (1974)
  Lincoln, Alfred W. (1961)
  Lincoln, Dick (1959)
  Lindekee, Mary Proal (1951)
  Lindley, Mr. and Mrs. Daniel (1955)
  Lindsay, G. Carroll (1955)
  Lindsay, Ian G. (1957)
  Lindsay, Joan R. (1949)
  Line, Ralph Marlow (1953)
  Linn, Janet Denithorne (1970)
  Lipman, Jean (1971)
  Lipman, Jonathan (1980)
  Lipstadt, Helene Rebecca (1976)
  Lisker, Albert (1953)
  Lisker and Lisker (1954)
  Liskowski, Bohdan (1961)
  Lissam, Simon (1965)
  Little and Ives Co. (1960)
  Little, Bertram (1960)
  Little, Sidney W. (1953-1955)
  Liverpool School of Architecture (1949, 1958, 1962-1963)
  Liverpool University Architecture Society (1955)
  Locchead, Kenneth (1952)
  Locke, Margaret E. (1949)
  Lockwood-Matthews Mansion (1973)
  Lo Curzio, Massimo (1965)
  Lodge, Henry Cabot (1950)
  Lodge, Sprucewold (1954)
  Loeb, Hermann (1946)
  Loeb, John (1974-1976, 1983)
  Loftstrom, Edward V. (1963)
  Logan, Ann M. (1955)
  London (1963)
  Long Island Antiquities, Society for the Preservation of (1969)
  Long, Susie (1949)
  Longhi, David (1959, 1974)
  Look Magazine (1962)
  Lord Travel Agency (1952, 1954)
  Loren, Erle (1955)
  Los Angeles (1972)
  Los Angeles County Museum (1955, 1958)
  Lotus (1964, 1970)
  Louisiana State University (1955, 1958)
  Louisville, J. B. Speed Art Museum (1952)
  Louisville, University of (1975)
  Louw, H. J. (1977)
  Love, Iris (1965)
  Lowd, Dana (1951)
  Lowe, David (1951-1954, 1975)
  Lowe, John (1955)
  Lowell, Isabel (1923)
  Lowenthal, Esther (1961, 1964, 1968-1969)
  Lowenthal, Helen (1951-1952, 1955-1956)
  Lowry, Bates (1966, 1972)
  Lubbock, Jules (1980)
  Lubetkin, Bertholde (1936, 1945-1946, undated)
  Lucas, Clive (1974)
  Lucas, Jannette (1948, 1950-1952)
  Luckhurst, K. W. (1951, 1955-1956)
  Luginbuhl, Viola (1962)
  Lukas, Gabriel (1969)
  Lukomski, George (1956)
  Luman, Thomas (1938)
  Lunn Travel (1962)
  Lurcat, Andre (1928, 1930, undated)
  Luty, Alan (1963)
  Luzuriaga, Carlos (1949)
  Lym, G. R. (1978)
  Lyman Allen Museum (1942, 1947, 1949, 1958)
  Lyman, Charles (1965)
  Lyman, Dwight C. (1955, 1973)
  Lynes, Russell (1973)
  Maas and Co. (1962)
  Maas, John (1957, 1966, 1969-1971)
  McAndrew, John (1940, 1945, 1949, 1953, 1957, 1969, 1978, 1981)
  McArthur, Shirley (1985)
  McAuley, Theodora (1962)
  McBreen (1949)
  McBride, Henry (1947)
  McCall's Magazine (1946)
  McCallum, Ian (1956, 1958-1959, 1963-1964)
  McCay, Mrs. A. B. (1948)
  McComb, Arthur (1945)
  McCormick, Margaret (1978)
  McCormick, Thomas J. (1948-1987, undated)
  McCosher, Delphina (1964)
  McCoubrey, John W. (1967)
  McCoy, Esther (1956, 1960)
  McCray, Porter (1956, 1969)
  McCullough, Jane Fiske (1966, 1968)
  McDonald (1978)
  McDonald, Thoreau (1949)
  McDonald, William L. (1955, 1963, 1982-1983)
  MacDougall, Elisabeth B. (1980)
  McGehee, Mary (1955)
  McGraw Hill Co. (1957, 1959,-1966)
  McGuire, Diane Kostial (1963)
  McGuire, William (1972)
  McIlhenny, Henry P. (1955, 1971)
  McIntyre, Ruth A. (1962)
  Mackay Brothers and Co. (1947)
  Mackay, David (1965-1966)
  Mackay-Smith, Alexander (1952-1953, 1962) (see also: Smith, Alexander Mackay)
  McKean, A. G. (1953)
  McKenna, Rosalie Thorne (Rollie) (1949-1958)
  McKibbin, David (1949, 1956, 1959, 1961)
  McKinley (1956)
  McKinley, Hazel G. (1964, 1979, 1981)
  Mackintosh Society (1963-1964)
  McLanathan, Richard B. K. (1958)
  MacLaren, Alistair (1960, 1962-1964, 1966, 1968, 1970)
  McMillan Co. (1953)
  Macmillan Encyclopedia of Architects (1980, 1982)
  Macmillan Publishers, Ltd. (1984)
  McNair, Andrew (1975)
  McNamara, Ellen 1974, 1976
  Macomber, C. Clark (1951)
  Macomber, Mr. and Mrs. Charles C. (1955)
  Macomber, Gail (1953)
  McQuade, Walter (1960)
  McReynolds, George (1952)
  Magazine of Art (1947-1953)
  Magaziner, Henry J. (1971-1973)
  Magee, John J. (1970)
  Magill, Peter (1951, 1955)
  Magruder, Charles (1957)
  Mahard, Francis M. (1968)
  Maher, Billy (undated)
  Maher, James T. (1981)
  Maher, William P. (1938)
  Maison du Libre (1951)
  Manchester Society of Architects, Student Association (1955)
  Mancini, Lillian (1951)
  Mancoff, Debra (1978)
  Mandell, Mrs. M. Hussey (1952)
  Mandell, Richard (1968)
  Mandelsohn, Louise (1955)
  Mang, Karl (1974)
  Manitoba, University of (1958-1959)
  Manning, Eileen (1952)
  Mansell Collection (1956-1958)
  Manson, Grant (1941, 1952, 1957-1958)
  Manuzio (1962)
  Maple and Co. (1946)
  Mar, Arxiu (1958)
  Marcus, Stanley (1962)
  Marden, Philip S. (1951)
  Marder, Tom (1979-1981)
  Marenco, Vittoria (1964)
  Mark, Edward L. (1966-1967)
  Markowitz, Arnold (1970)
  Mark Twain Memorial (1966-1970, 1975, 1977)
  Marlborough Fine Arts Ltd. (1962)
  Marlor, Clark S. (1969)
  Marmo (1962)
  Marquis, Alice (1986)
  Marquis Co. (1947- 1948)
  Marr, Harriet (1952)
  Marre, Robert de La (1927)
  Marsanas, Luis (1963-1964)
  Marshall, Percy Johnson (1959, 1963) (see also: Johnson-Marshall, Percy)
  Martienssen, Heather (1962)
  Martin, J. L. (1946-1947, 1952)
  Martin, J. R. (1965)
  Martin, Leslie (1954, 1957, 1959, 1962-1963)
  Martin, Thomas P. (1947)
  Martindale, Katharine (1960)
  Maryland Center for Public Broadcasting (1978)
  Maryland Historical Society (1957)
  Maryland State Library (1939)
  Marzoli, Carla C. (1954, 1956, 1958, 1964, 1968)
  Mas, Arxiu (1956)
  Masheck, Joseph (1970, 1973, 1977)
  Mason, Clark (1963-1964)
  Mason, Francis S. (1961-1965, 1967, 1979)
  Mason, Howard (1962)
  Massachusetts, Commonwealth of (1952, 1954)
  Massachusetts Hospital Service, Inc. (1954)
  Massachusetts Institute of Technology (1946-1952, 1954, 1958, 1962-1963, 1965-1973, 1975-1981)
  Massachusetts Motor Vehicle Assigned Risk Pool (1955)
  Massachusetts Review (1969)
  Massachusetts State Association of Architects (1954, 1957)
  Massachusetts Turnpike Authority (1959)
  Massachusetts, University of (1951, 1969)
  Massey, James C. (1963, 1966)
  Matheson, Donald W. (1980)
  Matheson, Martin (1966)
  Mattingly, Garrett (1946)
  Maufe, Edward (1960)
  Maunoury, Jean (1948)
  Maxant, Harriett (1967)
  Maxon, John (1961)
  Maxtone-Graham, John (1974)
  Maxwell, Clifford (1975, 1977, 1981)
  Maxwell Mansion (1971)
  May, John S. (1955)
  Mayer, Grace M. (1953)
  Mayflower Descendants, Society of (1944-1945, 1947-1950, 1952, 1954, 1956, 1959, 1963, 1966-1968, 1970, 1973-1975)
  Mayher, Phil (1952)
  Mayne, Jonathan (1962)
  Mead, Katherine (1964, 1967)
  Medicare/Blue Shield (1971-1972, 1985) (see also: Blue Cross/Blue Shield)
  Meehan, Patrick J. (1984)
  Meeks, Carroll (1944-1966, undated)
  Meigs, Walter (1954)
  Meijburn, Herm. van der Kloot (1927)
  Meiss, Millard (1952, 1960, 1962- 1963)
  Melbourne, University of (1958)
  Mellon, Tom (1962)
  Mellquist, Jerome (1955-1956, 1958)
  Mendelsohn, Eric (1953)
  Mendelsohn, Frances (1959)
  Mendenhall (1964)
  Menges, Axel (1986)
  Meredith Press (1962)
  Meriden Gravure Co. (1960)
  Merkel, Jayne (1967)
  Merrill, David O. (1960)
  Mesevery, Robert (1956)
  Metcalf Printing (1973)
  Metcalf, Priscilla (1956-1957, 1962-1963, 1966-1968, 1977)
  Metropolitan Museum of Art (1951, 1968-1970, 1972-1973, 1979-1980, 1982)
  Meyer, B. A. (1946)
  Meyer, Charles (1961)
  Miami, University of (1972)
  Michalski, Thomas (1976)
  Michigan, University of (1928, 1947-1948, 1965-1966, 1970)
  Microcard Committee (1951)
  Microcard Foundation (1948)
  Middlesex Hospital (1938, 1941, 1945)
  Middlesex School Alumni Bulletin (1952)
  Middleton, Robin (1956-1961, 1963-1967, 1969, 1971-1972, 1978)
  Middletown Press (1945)
  Mies van der Rohe (1947)
  Miles, H. (1961)
  Miles, Hamish (1965, 1966)
  Miles, James (1946)
  Miles, Jean (1960)
  Millar, John F. (1980-1983)
  Millar, Olive (1952)
  Millech, Knud (1930, 1956)
  Miller Co. (1945, 1947-1952, 1955)
  Miller, Dorothy (1961)
  Miller, Herman (1963)
  Miller, Janet (1978)
  Miller, Meredith (1958-1959)
  Miller, R. Craig (1973-1978, 1981-1984, 1986)
  Miller, Mrs. Russ (1958)
  Miller, Stephen R. (1976- 1977)
  Millett, Fred B. (1949, 1963)
  Millon, Henry A. (1956, 1964, 1966-1967, 1978, 1980-1981, 1983)
  Millon, Henry A. and Judy (1973)
  Millon, Judy (1982, 1984)
  Milne-Henderson, Pat (1960, 1962) (see also: Henderson, Pat Milne)
  Milwaukee Art Center (1977)
  Milwaukee Public Library (1952)
  Minard, Ralph (1963)
  Mindlin, Henrique E. (1955)
  Minneapolis City Planning Department (1969)
  Minneapolis Institute of Arts (1941, 1956, 1959)
  Minnesota Society of Architects (1958)
  Minnesota, University of (1944, 1946-1947, 1949-1950, 1955, 1958, 1961-1962, 1969, 1972, 1985)
  Minnick, Margaret (1979-1981)
  Minton, Lee R. (1973)
  Mississippi State College for Women (1947)
  Mitchell, Allen (1963)
  Mitchell, Anthon (1952)
  Mitchell, Charles (1962, 1974)
  Mitchell, Herbert (1969, 1975)
  Mitchell, Robert D. (1970)
  Mitchell, Shirley Spratt (1968)
  Mock, Betty (1947, 1949-1951)
  Modern Age (1962)
  Modern Architecture (1943, 1945)
  Modern Architecture Symposium (1962, 1964, 1966)
  Moe, Henry Allen (1953, 1963, 1968)
  Moeller, Achim F. (1973)
  Moholy-Nagy, Sibyl (1969, 1971)
  Mohr, Elizabeth Heaton (1963)
  Moise, Howard (1951)
  Moller, C. F. (1956)
  Moltke, J. W. (1971)
  Mongan, Agnes (1944-1948, 1950-1955, 1963, 1969, 1973)
  Mongan, Elizabeth (1945)
  Monkhouse, Christopher P. (1982)